So I just came on here to tell y'all that my show in Baltimore tonight has been canceled due to unforeseen circumstances.
And hey, Ashley, and I'm probably going to cancel the tour.
And and so, you know, Baltimore, y'all always show me so much motherfucking love, man.
You really do.
Y'all show me so, so much love.
So I really I'm really salty about having to cancel this.
OK, so the reason why it was being it's being canceled is because I was told that somebody was covering the cost of the rental.
And then I found out today that they're not that they didn't cover the cost of the rental.
And I just I don't I don't make anything.
Unfortunately, you know, I don't I don't I don't make anything on these shows.
I barely I mean, I'm in the red.
And so that help is what allows me to be able to, you know, do the shows for free.
And so when that fell through, it's like if if you're not covering the rental fee for the venue,
um, what are we doing?
Um, oh, I don't ever give up hope.
I'm just irritated.
But one thing I do know is that everything that happens to me happens for me.
Um, and so this will encourage me to figure out another, um, another way forward.
And I have been challenged to figure out how to give you all the work.
I'm not going to start selling tickets because I'm not going to live on this planet doing shit.
I don't want to fucking do unless it is for the sake of helping others.
So, no, I'm not going to start selling tickets, at least not in that traditional fashion.
I've done it.
I did it.
I hate it.
Um, so, no, um, it, and unless you have ever done it, but trust me, don't speak on it because
I've done years and years and years and years and years of selling tickets.
And so, um, someone asked, why do I hate it?
So, basically, one of the reasons I hate it is because it requires marketing on a level
that I consider to be harassment.
It is very, um, noisy out here in general.
And it becomes this, like, requirement to be louder than the noise.
And in order to be louder than the noise, you have to just be just on, just over and
over, just on top of it.
And, and like, it's not like you're, it's not like sharing music, right?
Where you just keep sharing and sharing the music because the music is, there's so many
ways to share it.
No, you're having to, like, keep sharing, like, come see me, come see me, come see me.
And it's, it's just, it's, it doesn't feel restorative to me or to you.
And I've done it for years and years.
The other part of it is that, you know, it fails a lot.
And the, and the last part of it is y'all don't got money.
You know, there's, there's just the reality that I am aware of my surroundings and of
my people and that y'all don't have fucking money.
Hey, Ann.
It's like, how am I gonna be out here?
I'm not these other artists.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm very fortunate to have many methods that I can move through to
encourage you all in exchange, right?
So whether it's books, whether it's art, et cetera.
And, um, I know y'all don't have money because I don't, I am literally just living off of my
insecure funds, my, my Patreon, I'm losing like hundreds of followers a month and I don't
know why.
And I can only assume it's because folks don't got fucking money.
And that's the intention.
That's the goal, right?
To make everybody have to keep giving up things to trade, to, to, to, to, to try to like, hold
on, right?
So as an artist, I'm just constantly trying to figure out how to create spaces that enrich
us to fucking fight and to also still create and create in the methodology that we create
in.
All of us are creators.
So it's not necessarily like you have to be an artist to be a creative.
So, you know, this is, this is symptomatic of a bigger thing.
Like my life is not lived for me.
My life is lived for the world.
So that's always been the case.
Shit that happens to me, it happens to me first.
And then I see it happen to everyone around me.
So shit happening to me.
And I don't mean on a, like a basic space of like, um, um, I mean something like Trent,
like, um, awakenings.
Right.
So listen, let's, someone said they had to borrow from the 401k, you and me both.
I literally am like, I have to hit my financial planner.
Like how much I could have without us being in like a bind.
Um, so, so the Baltimore show is canceled.
I, I'm probably going to have to cancel the tour.
I don't live the same life I used to live as a touring comic, et cetera.
I mean, there was a time where your girl was out here and part of me wonders if the series
of events taking place are, well, they are, it's always a bigger, it's always a bigger message.
And I'm just trying to make sure I interpret it correctly.
Thank you, Mr. Black and Famous for buying a badge.
Um, and so stay tuned.
I will never give up.
It may look different.
It may feel different.
I will never give up.
And even when I leave this realm, I will never give up.
Because all I'm doing is taking over energy that was here before and continuing it.
So I didn't even start this shit.
I am of the continuance.
So I will never give up.
I take everything, like I said before, everything that happens to me happens for me.
Um, I know this, I feel this, I will blood bend the ops to sito.
Someone was at the Harlem show.
And, um, make it neurodivergent.
Correct.
For those who understand, an old world is being left behind.
And if, if you're meant for the new one, you, you really realize that if you don't leave it, it'll get taken from you.
So stay lifted.
If you know people in Baltimore that were planning on coming, please spread the word.
And stay alert.
You know?
Well, the signs are always around you.
They're everywhere.
And they're loud.
They're loud.
You're on the other side of the bookcase.
Listen.
Okay?
Truth Translator is absolutely going to be streaming.
I uploaded it yesterday.
But you can also get it for free on Bandcamp right now.
But yes, it is absolutely going to be streaming.
Uh, the show is canceled because
I was told that someone was going to
be covering the cost of the venue rental.
And they,
I learned this morning that they are not.
And I cannot afford to.
Oh, thank you, Brian.
Brian.
So, I'll tap back in.
Please, um, sign up for my newsletter so that you can
know when I'm going to figure,
so you can know when I do figure a substitution
or a scenario or something out.
Okay?
Um, my intuition says I'm not supposed to be on tour.
That's what my intuition says.
That I'm not supposed to be on tour.
Thank you, Jessme.
Received.
Karen Chantel asked,
can I do it from my living room?
So, Karen, this is a stage.
I literally bought a stage.
Like, literally.
I bought a stage.
So, yes.
I could do it from my living room.
Okay.
I love you.
I appreciate you.
Wait on it said.
A little commotion for the dress.
Weekly sessions.
Okay.
I'm going to figure this out.
You guys.
Usually Instagram is a heap of trash.
And here you are.
being the exact opposite.
So, that says something.